Guide to the John Taber papers, 1880-1965.
Taber, John papers
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
John Taber papers, 1880-1965.
2202
John, Taber 1880-1965.
240 linear ft.
Correspondence, Printed Materials
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Files include correspondence with constituents, colleagues, special interest groups and others; memoranda and statistical information; press releases and copies of speeches; printed House and Senate bills and committe reports; and pamphlets and clippings concerning congressional committees, legislation under consideration, and numerous items of public interest, both to the nation as a whole and to his constituency. Also correspondence, deed searches, and other papers, 1919-1946, of the law firm, Taber and Parker, and occasional personal papers of Representative Taber.
BIOGRAPHICAL NOTE
Lawyer, legislator; U.S. Congressman from Auburn, New York (1923-1963).
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Files include correspondence with constituents, colleagues, special interest groups and others; memoranda and statistical information; press releases and copies of speeches; printed House and Senate bills and committe reports; and pamphlets and clippings concerning congressional committees, legislation under consideration, and numerous items of public interest, both to the nation as a whole and to his constituency. Also correspondence, deed searches, and other papers, 1919-1946, of the law firm, Taber and Parker, and occasional personal papers of Representative Taber.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Taber, John,1880-1965.; Taber and Parker (Firm); United States.Congress.House.; United States.Congress--Leadership.; United States.Congress.House--Public relations.; United States.Congress--Constituent communication.
Subjects:
Legislators--United States.
Places:
United States--Politics and government--20th century.; Auburn (N.Y.)--Politics and government.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CONTAINER LIST
- Legislative Related Materials, 1941-1959
  Includes some Apropriations material.
  Arranged chronologically and then alphabetically.
  - West Point, Examinations and Appointments, 1936-1942 (Box 52)
  - West Point, Examinations and Appointments, 1936-1942 (Box 53)
  - Envelopes, folders, and bundles of petitions relating to different or proposed legislation, 1939-1942 (Box 63)
  - Envelopes, folders, and bundles of petitions relating to different or proposed legislation, 1939-1942 (Box 64)
  - Education, 1941 (Box 87)
  - Relief Bill, 1941 (Box 87)
  - Miscellaneous, 1942 (Box 88)
  - P.O. 1942, 1942 (Box 88)
  - Treasury P.O., 1942 (Box 87)
  - Envelope, "Inflation Bill Farm Parity", 1942-09-25 (Box 87)
  - Pamphlet - Biographical register of the Dept. of State, 1944-09-01 (Box 75)
  - Civil Service, 1945-1947 (Box 161)
  - Feed and Grains, 1945-1948 (Box 161)
  - Foreign Affairs, 1945-1947 (Box 161)
  - Miscellaneous 1945 Appropriations, 1945 (Box 77)
  - O.P.A., 1945-1948 (Box 161)
  - Pamphlet - Foreign service list, 1945-01-01 (Box 75)
  - Pamphlet - Foreign service list abridged, 1945-10-01 (Box 75)
  - Agriculture, 1946-1947 (Box 161)
  - Agriculture, 1946 (Box 76)
  - Appropriations, 1946 (Box 76)
  - Appropriations, Agriculture, 1946 (Box 77)
  - Appropriations, British Loan, 1946 (Box 77)
  - Appropriations, Burton, L. French, 1946 (Box 77)
  - Appropriations, Coast Guard, 1946 (Box 77)
  - Appropriations, Corporation, 1946 (Box 77)
  - Appropriations, Indian Affairs, 1946 (Box 77)
  - Appropriations, Interior, 1946 (Box 77)
  - Appropriations, Labor Federal Security, 1946 (Box 77)
  - Appropriations, Legislative, 1946 (Box 77)
  - Appropriations, Navy, 1946 (Box 77)
  - Appropriations, Personnel of Committee, 1946 (Box 77)
  - Appropriations, Recession first of 1946, 1946 (Box 77)
  - Appropriations, State and Justice, 1946 (Box 77)
  - Appropriations, State Justice and Committee, 1946 (Box 77)
  - Appropriations, Treasury and Post Office, 1946 (Box 77)
  - Appropriations, War, 1946 (Box 77)
  - Atomic Energy, 1946 (Box 76)
  - Banking and Currency, 1946 (Box 76)
  - Byrd Commission, 1946 (Box 76)
  - Campaign Expenditures, 1946 (Box 76)
  - Commodity Credit Corporation, 1946 (Box 74)
  - Dumbarton Oaks, 1946 (Box 76)
  - Education, 1946 (Box 76)
  - Envelope - Office of War I Formation, 1946 (Box 75)
  - Federal Communications Commission, 1946 (Box 74)
  - General Work of Committee Appropriations, 1946 (Box 77)
  - Housing, 1946-1947 (Box 161)
  - Housing, 1946 (Box 76)
  - Housing, 1946 (Box 74)
  - Interstate and Foreign Commerce Commission, 1946-1947 (Box 161)
  - Judiciary, 1946 (Box 76)
  - Labor, 1946 (Box 76)
  - Lend-Lease, 1946 (Box 161)
  - Letters regarding Bill 752, 1946 (Box 76)
  - Letters regarding Railroad Retirements, 1946 (Box 76)
  - Liquor, 1946 (Box 76)
  - Maritime Commission, 1946 (Box 74)
  - Military Affairs, 1946 (Box 76)
  - Miscellaneous Legislation, 1946 (Box 76)
  - O.P.A., 1946 (Box 76)
  - O.P.A., General, 1946 (Box 76)
  - O.P.A., Price of feed-corn, 1946 (Box 76)
  - Office Price Administration, 1946 (Box 74)
  - Package addressed to the Hon. A. W. Bennett from Hamilton Fish, 1946 (Box 75)
  - R.E.A., 1946 (Box 77)
  - Rivers and Harbors, 1946 (Box 76)
  - Roads, 1946 (Box 76)
  - Small Business Committee, 1946 (Box 76)
  - Smaller War Plants, 1946 (Box 77)
  - Social Security, 1946 (Box 76)
  - U.N.O., 1946 (Box 77)
  - U.N.R.R.A., 1946 (Box 75)
  - United Nations Relief Rehabilitation Reports, 1946 (Box 77)
  - Veterans, 1946 (Box 76)
  - War Manpower Committee, 1946 (Box 77)
  - War Shipping Administration, 1946 (Box 77)
  - War Shipping Administration, 1946 (Box 75)
  - Ways and Means, 1946 (Box 76)
  - Armed Services, 1947-1948 (Box 161)
  - Flood Control, 1947 (Box 161)
  - Food Study Hoover, 1947 (Box 161)
  - Greece, Turkey, 1947-1948 (Box 42)
  - Immigration, 1947-1951 (Box 145)
  - Judiciary, 1947 (Box 161)
  - Labor, Education, 1947 (Box 161)
  - Marshall Plan, 1947-1948 (Box 42)
  - Military Affairs, 1947 (Box 161)
  - Miscellaneous Legislative, 1947 (Box 161)
  - Post Office, 1947 (Box 161)
  - Rent Control, 1947 (Box 161)
  - State Department, 1947 (Box 161)
  - Tennessee Valley, 1947 (Box 161)
  - Transfer Postal Accounts, 1947 (Box 161)
  - Veterans Affairs, 1947 (Box 161)
  - Ways and Means, 1947 (Box 161)
  - Agriculture, 1948 (Box 42)
  - Civil Rights, 1948 (Box 161)
  - Civil Service, 1948 (Box 42)
  - Foreign Affairs, 1948 (Box 42)
  - International Information and Cultural Affairs, 1948 (Box 42)
  - Interstate and Foreign Commerce, 1948 (Box 42)
  - Labor Department, 1948 (Box 42)
  - Post Office, 1948 (Box 42)
  - Public Lands and Public Works, 1948 (Box 42)
  - State Department, 1948 (Box 42)
  - UnAmerican Affairs, 1948 (Box 42)
  - Ways and Means, 1948 (Box 42)
  - Agriculture, 1955 (Box 17)
  - Banking and Currency, 1955 (Box 17)
  - Banks, 1955 (Box 17)
  - Bills and resolutions, 1955 (Box 17)
  - Civil Service, 1955 (Box 17)
  - Commentary re statements of JT, 1955 (Box 17)
  - Congressional Committee, 1955 (Box 17)
  - Department of Defense, 1955 (Box 17)
  - Dixon, Yates, 1955 (Box 17)
  - Federal Spending Facts, 1955 (Box 17)
  - Foreign Affairs, 1955 (Box 17)
  - Immigration, 1955 (Box 17)
  - Interior Department, 1955 (Box 17)
  - Interstate and Foreign Commerce, 1955 (Box 17)
  - Judiciary, 1955 (Box 17)
  - Labor, 1955 (Box 17)
  - Leonard Jasciewicz, 1955 (Box 11)
  - Mailing List, JT, 1955 (Box 17)
  - Miscellaneous Legislation, 1955 (Box 17)
  - Natural Gas, 1955 (Box 17)
  - Niagara Power, 1955 (Box 17)
  - Office of the Clerk, 1955 (Box 17)
  - Public Works, 1955 (Box 17)
  - Publications, 1955 (Box 17)
  - Publicity, 1955 (Box 17)
  - Refugee Relief, 1955 (Box 17)
  - Reorganization Act, 1955 (Box 17)
  - Republican National Committee, 1955 (Box 17)
  - Senate Bills, 1955 (Box 17)
  - Social Security, 1955 (Box 17)
  - Statements of JT, 1955 (Box 17)
  - Veterans Survivors Benefits Acts, 1955 (Box 17)
  - Voting records - Mr. Taber, 1955 (Box 17)
  - Ways and Means - House Bills, 1955 (Box 17)
  - White House, 1955 (Box 17)
  - Agricultural Year Books, 1957 (Box 14)
    1957 and prior years
  - House Floor 1957 (out of a place), 1957 (Box 3)
  - Pamphlet - The Railroad Retirement and Unemployment Insurance Systems, 1957-1958, 1957-1958 (Box 13)
  - School Aid Bill, 1957 (Box 7)
  - Veterans Affairs (all individual folders), 1957 (Box 173)
  - 1958 Appropriations, 1958 (Box 9)
  - 1958 Appropriations, 1958 (Box 10)
  - 85th Congress House Bills, First Session, 1958 (Box 3)
  - Acknowledgements, 1958 (Box 14)
  - Acknowledgements (4 folders), 1958 (Box 13)
  - Agriculture Department, 1958 (Box 14)
  - Appointments, 1958 (Box 14)
  - Atomic Energy Commission, 1958 (Box 14)
  - Attwater, J. Dwight, 1958 (Box 11)
  - Auburn Office, 1958 (Box 14)
  - Auburn Radio Tower, 1958 (Box 8)
  - Berdard F. Zuccardy, 1958 (Box 11)
  - Braverman, Edward, 1958 (Box 11)
  - Brock, Walter B., 1958 (Box 11)
  - Brussels Fair, 1958 (Box 14)
  - Buffalo Chamber of Commerce, 1958 (Box 14)
  - Buffalo Harbor, 1958 (Box 14)
  - Capitol, 1958 (Box 14)
  - Central Intelligence Agency, 1958 (Box 14)
  - Charles Magavero, 1958 (Box 11)
  - Civil Aeronautics, 1958 (Box 14)
  - Civil Defense, 1958 (Box 14)
  - Civil Service Employment, 1958 (Box 14)
  - Civil Service General, 1958 (Box 14)
  - Clippings, 1958 (Box 14)
  - Commerce Department, 1958 (Box 14)
  - Condolences, 1958 (Box 14)
  - Congressional Record, 1958 (Box 14)
  - Conrad, Dorothy, 1958 (Box 11)
  - Corps of Engineers, 1958 (Box 14)
  - D.A.R., 1958 (Box 14)
  - Defense Department, 1958 (Box 14)
  - Defense Department - Legislation, 1958 (Box 3)
  - Dolgin, George, 1958 (Box 11)
  - Donovan, Eugene C., 1958 (Box 11)
  - Employment, 1958 (Box 14)
  - Federal Communications Comnission, 1958 (Box 14)
  - Federal Housing Administration, 1958 (Box 14)
  - Federal Power Commission, 1958 (Box 14)
  - Federal Trade Commission, 1958 (Box 14)
  - Finger Lakes, 1958 (Box 14)
  - Foreign Affairs, 1958 (Box 3)
  - Foreign Affairs, 1958 (Box 3)
  - Foreman, Paul Wesley, 1958 (Box 11)
  - General Services Administration, 1958 (Box 14)
  - George Williams, 1958 (Box 11)
  - Gordon, Janet Hill, 1958 (Box 11)
  - H.E.W., 1958 (Box 3)
  - H.E.W., 1958 (Box 3)
  - H.R. 758, 1958 (Box 3)
  - Herron, George, 1958 (Box 11)
  - Higbie, C. L., 1958 (Box 11)
  - Highway Bills, 1958 (Box 3)
  - Highway Legislation, 1958 (Box 3)
  - House Administration, 1958 (Box 3)
  - House Bills 1958 end of June 85th Second, 1958 (Box 3)
  - House Bills 85th Second, 1958 (Box 3)
  - House Floor, 1958 (Box 3)
  - Immigration, 1958 (Box 3)
  - Immigration, 1958 (Box 6)
  - Industrial Survey - Auburn, 1958 (Box 3)
  - Industrial Survey - Cortland, 1958 (Box 3)
  - Industrial Survey - Ithaca, 1958 (Box 3)
  - Industrial Survey - Macedon, 1958 (Box 3)
  - Industrial Survey - Montour Falls, 1958 (Box 3)
  - Industrial Survey - Watkins Glen, 1958 (Box 3)
  - Interior, 1958 (Box 3)
  - Internal Revenue, Mount Roy, 1958 (Box 11)
  - Interstate and Foreign Commerce, 1958 (Box 3)
  - J. Karpinski, 1958 (Box 11)
  - John McCarthy, 1958 (Box 11)
  - Judiciary, 1958 (Box 6)
  - Ken Keady, 1958 (Box 11)
  - Knight, Francis, 1958 (Box 11)
  - Kress, Charles, 1958 (Box 11)
  - Labor, 1958 (Box 6)
  - Labor, 1958 (Box 6)
  - Legislation - Civil Rights, 1958 (Box 3)
  - Legislative, 1958 (Box 3)
  - Legislative, 1958 (Box 6)
  - Legislative, 1958 (Box 6)
  - Legislative Miscellaneous, 1958 (Box 6)
  - Legislative Miscellaneous, 1958 (Box 7)
  - Legislative Miscellaneous, end of June, end of Session, 1958 (Box 6)
  - Levin, Jack, 1958 (Box 11)
  - Mailing list statements of JT (empty folder), 1958 (Box 7)
  - McLeod, Clarence, 1958 (Box 11)
  - Middle East, 1958 (Box 6)
  - Minority Clerk Job, 1958 (Box 7)
  - Miscellaneous, 1958 (Box 6)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence Files, A-Z, 1958 (Box 13)
  - Nadolski, Stanley, 1958 (Box 11)
  - Niagara, 1958 (Box 7)
  - Niagara Power, 1958 (Box 7)
  - Office for Clerk, 1958 (Box 7)
  - Office of Clerk, 1958 (Box 7)
  - Pamphlet - Trade Report from 1,041 U.S. Cities, 1958 (Box 13)
  - Pencil notes of Mr. Taber, 1958 (Box 7)
  - Private Bills, 1958 (Box 7)
  - Private bills, 1958 (Box 7)
  - Procino, Rossi, 1958 (Box 11)
  - Public Works, 1958 (Box 7)
  - Public Works, 1958 (Box 7)
  - Railroads, 1958 (Box 7)
  - Red Star, 1958 (Box 11)
  - Refugee Relief Act, 1958 (Box 7)
  - Republican Congressional Committee, 1958 (Box 7)
  - Republican Congressional Committee, 1958 (Box 7)
  - Republican National Committee, 1958 (Box 7)
  - Republican National Committee, 1958 (Box 7)
  - Retirement Pensions, 1958 (Box 7)
  - Rules, 1958 (Box 7)
  - Schaeffer, John J., 1958 (Box 11)
  - Schaeffer, John J., 1958 (Box 11)
  - School Aid Bill, 1958 (Box 7)
  - Senate Bills 85th Second Session, 1958 (Box 8)
  - Senate Bills, 85th Congress, First Session, 1958 (Box 7)
  - Shuler, Virginia, 1958 (Box 11)
  - Social Security, 1958 (Box 7)
  - Social Security, 1958 (Box 7)
  - Statements, 1958 (Box 8)
  - Statements, 1958 (Box 8)
  - Theobald, Richard, 1958 (Box 11)
  - U.S. Hoffman Machinery Corporation, 1958 (Box 11)
  - Van Rensselaer, Bernard, 1958 (Box 11)
  - Veterans, 1958 (Box 8)
  - Veterans, 1958 (Box 8)
  - Voting Records, 1958 (Box 8)
  - Ways and Means, 1958 (Box 8)
  - Ways and Means, 1958 (Box 8)
  - Ways and Means, 1958 (Box 8)
  - Ways and Means from end of June, 1958 (Box 8)
  - Wheeler, Emmet, 1958 (Box 11)
  - White House, 1958 (Box 8)
  - White House, 1958 (Box 8)
  - William Cosgrove, Geneva Milk Company, 1958 (Box 11)
  - William Wetzel, 1958 (Box 11)
  - WMBO - Keesee, Fred, 1958 (Box 8)
  - Yameen, Miss Affiffi (Closed), 1958 (Box 11)
  - Zehring, Robert, 1958 (Box 11)
  - Alphabetical listing, 19 folders, A-Z, 1959 (Box 5)
  - Defense Department, 1959 (Box 4)
  - Department of Health, Education and Welfare, 1959 (Box 4)
  - Employment, 1959 (Box 4)
  - Federal Aviation Agency, 1959 (Box 4)
  - Federal Communications Commission, 1959 (Box 4)
  - Fish and Wild Life, 1959 (Box 4)
  - Flags, 1959 (Box 4)
  - General Accounting, 1959 (Box 4)
  - General Services Administration, 1959 (Box 4)
  - Government Printing Office, 1959 (Box 4)
  - Housing, 1959 (Box 4)
  - Interior Department, 1959 (Box 4)
  - Internal Revenue, 1959 (Box 4)
  - International Cooperation Administration, 1959 (Box 4)
  - Interstate Commerce Commission, 1959 (Box 4)
  - Invitations Accepted, 1959 (Box 4)
  - Invitations Declined, 1959 (Box 4)
  - Labor Department, 1959 (Box 4)
  - Letters from Members, 1959 (Box 4)
  - Letters to Members, 1959 (Box 4)
  - Library of Congress, 1959 (Box 4)
  - Milk Producers, 1959 (Box 4)
  - Miscellaneous, 1959 (Box 4)
  - N.L.R.B., 1959 (Box 5)
  - N.Y. Port Authority, 1959 (Box 5)
  - N.Y. Republican Delegation, 1959 (Box 4)
  - N.Y.S., 1959 (Box 5)
  - N.Y.S. Matters, 1959 (Box 4)
  - N.Y.S. Roads, 1959 (Box 5)
  - National Aeronautics Space Administration, 1959 (Box 4)
  - National Federation of Independent Business, 1959 (Box 4)
  - National Science Foundation, 1959 (Box 5)
  - New York Republican Commission, 1959 (Box 5)
  - News Letters, 1959 (Box 5)
  - Page Requests, 1959 (Box 5)
  - Passports, 1959 (Box 5)
  - Patent Office, 1959 (Box 5)
  - Phone Calls, 1959 (Box 5)
  - Publications, 1959 (Box 5)
  - Radio Broadcasts, 1959 (Box 5)
  - Recommendations, 1959 (Box 5)
  - Referrals, 1959 (Box 5)
  - Republican Whip, 1959 (Box 5)
  - Seneca Ordinance, 1959 (Box 5)
  - Small Business Administration, 1959 (Box 5)
  - Social Security, 1959 (Box 5)
  - Stats Department, 1959 (Box 5)
  - Tours, 1959 (Box 5)
  - U.S. Information Agency, 1959 (Box 5)
  - Unemployment, 1959 (Box 5)
  - United Nations, 1959 (Box 5)
  - Ag. Appropriations Bill, Date Unknown (Box 87)
  - Agriculture, Date Unknown (Box 87)
  - Agriculture, Date Unknown (Box 87)
  - Appropriation, Date Unknown (Box 42)
  - Appropriations Miscellaneous, Date Unknown (Box 87)
  - Appropriations, general, Date Unknown (Box 87)
  - Atomic Energy Commission, Date Unknown (Box 42)
  - Austria, Date Unknown (Box 144)
  - Banking and Currency, Date Unknown (Box 87)
  - Banking and Currency, Date Unknown (Box 42)
  - Barger Papers, Date Unknown (Box 59)
  - Belgium, Date Unknown (Box 144)
  - Bills by Mr. Taber, Date Unknown (Box 87)
  - Budget, Date Unknown (Box 87)
  - Bunch of telegrams to Mr. Taber, Date Unknown (Box 87)
  - Bundles of broadcasts and releases, Date Unknown (Box 59)
  - Bundles of broadcasts and releases, Date Unknown (Box 60)
  - Civil Defense, Date Unknown (Box 88)
  - Combined Miscellaneous Legislation, Date Unknown (Box 42)
  - Conscription, Date Unknown (Box 87)
  - Defense Program, Date Unknown (Box 87)
  - Deficiency Appropriation, Date Unknown (Box 87)
  - District of Columbia, Date Unknown (Box 42)
  - Economy Special Joint Committee, Date Unknown (Box 88)
  - Education, Date Unknown (Box 42)
  - Foreign Affairs, Date Unknown (Box 88)
  - France, Date Unknown (Box 144)
  - Germany I, Date Unknown (Box 144)
  - Germany II, Date Unknown (Box 144)
  - Greece, Date Unknown (Box 144)
  - H.E.H., Date Unknown (Box 59)
  - Harry Barger, Date Unknown (Box 59)
  - Interstate Commerce, Date Unknown (Box 88)
  - Italy, Date Unknown (Box 144)
  - Joint Income Tax, Date Unknown (Box 87)
  - Judiciary, Date Unknown (Box 88)
  - Judiciary, Date Unknown (Box 42)
  - Labor, Date Unknown (Box 87)
  - Labor, Date Unknown (Box 88)
  - Legislative Appropriations, Date Unknown (Box 87)
  - Lend-Lease, Date Unknown (Box 87)
  - Mer. Marine & Fisheries, Date Unknown (Box 42)
  - Military Affairs, Date Unknown (Box 87)
  - Military Affairs, Date Unknown (Box 88)
  - Miscellaneous, Date Unknown (Box 87)
  - Naval Affairs, Date Unknown (Box 88)
  - Neutrality, Date Unknown (Box 87)
  - Oswego Project, Date Unknown (Box 88)
  - Paul B. Paters, Date Unknown (Box 87)
  - Postal, Date Unknown (Box 88)
  - Report of Conference of Congressman Taber's Committee and OMGUS (Office of Military Government for Germany [U.S.]), Date Unknown (Box 144)
  - Reports and Hearings, Date Unknown (Box 57)
  - Reports and Hearings, Date Unknown (Box 58)
  - Rivers and Harbors, Date Unknown (Box 87)
  - Sheppard, Houstonville, Date Unknown (Box 88)
  - Social Security, Date Unknown (Box 87)
  - St. Lawrence Waterway, Date Unknown (Box 88)
  - Taxes, Date Unknown (Box 87)
  - Trieste, Date Unknown (Box 144)
  - Turkey, Date Unknown (Box 144)
  - Veterans Affairs, Date Unknown (Box 88)
  - Veterans Affairs, Date Unknown (Box 42)
  - W.P.A., Date Unknown (Box 87)
  - War Referendum, Date Unknown (Box 87)
  - Ways and Means, Date Unknown (Box 88)
  - Wheat, Date Unknown (Box 88)
  - Taber Speeches
    - 1942 and prior, 1923-1942 (Box 174)
    - 1943 (Box 174)
    - 1944 and 1945, 1944-1945 (Box 174)
    - 1946 (Box 174)
    - Campaign, City, State and Federal, 1947 (Box 174)
    - 1947, May 30 onward, 1947-05-30 (Box 174)
    - 1947, January to May 30, 1947-01-1947-05-30 (Box 174)
    - Campaign, Date Unknown (Box 174)
    - Communism in Action, Date Unknown (Box 174)
    - District of Columbia (sub-committee), Date Unknown (Box 174)
    - Speeches, Undated, Date Unknown (Box 174)
    - Statistics on the Congressional Election of November 5, 1946, Date Unknown (Box 174)
  - Memorial Addresses Delivered in Congress
    - A. B. Kelly - Pennysylvania, Date Unknown (Box 164)
    - A. H. Anderson - Minnesota, Date Unknown (Box 164)
    - A. M. Fernandez - New Mexico, Date Unknown (Box 164)
    - A. S. Camp - Georgia, Date Unknown (Box 164)
    - B. C. Reece - Tennessee, Date Unknown (Box 164)
    - B. R. Maybank - S. Carolina, Date Unknown (Box 164)
    - C. Hinshaw - California, Date Unknown (Box 164)
    - C. R. Hoey - N. Carolina, Date Unknown (Box 164)
    - C. W. Reed - Illinois, Date Unknown (Box 164)
    - D. A. Reed - New York, Date Unknown (Box 164)
    - D. H. Elliott - Pennsylvania, Date Unknown (Box 164)
    - D. M. Hall - N. Carolina, Date Unknown (Box 164)
    - D. P. Griswold - Nebraska, Date Unknown (Box 164)
    - G. S. Long - Louisiana, Date Unknown (Box 164)
    - H. A. Butler - Nebraska, Date Unknown (Box 164)
    - H. L. Lanham - Georgia, Date Unknown (Box 164)
    - H. M. Kilgore - W. Virginia, Date Unknown (Box 164)
    - J. B. Bowler - Illinois, Date Unknown (Box 164)
    - J. D. Dingell - Michigan, Date Unknown (Box 164)
    - J. J. Riley - S. Carolina, Date Unknown (Box 164)
    - J. R. Farrington - Hawaii, Date Unknown (Box 164)
    - L. C. Hunt - Wyoming, Date Unknown (Box 164)
    - L. C. Rabaut - Michigan, Date Unknown (Box 164)
    - L. H. Wisconsin - Wisconsin, Date Unknown (Box 164)
    - O. Brooks - Louisiana, Date Unknown (Box 164)
    - P. A. McCarran - Nevada, Date Unknown (Box 164)
    - P. W. Shafer - Michigan, Date Unknown (Box 164)
    - R. L. Neuberger - Oregon, Date Unknown (Box 164)
    - R. M. Keeney - Illinois, Date Unknown (Box 164)
    - R. V. Mack - Washington, Date Unknown (Box 164)
    - S. B. Carter - Iowa, Date Unknown (Box 164)
    - S. C. Simpson - Illinois, Date Unknown (Box 164)
    - V. D. Buchanan - Pennsylvania, Date Unknown (Box 164)
    - W. E. McVey - Illinois, Date Unknown (Box 164)
    - W. F. Norrell - Arkansas, Date Unknown (Box 164)
    - W. K. Scott - N. Carolina, Date Unknown (Box 164)
    - W. Langer - N. Dakota, Date Unknown (Box 164)
    - W. T. Granahan - Pennsylvania, Date Unknown (Box 164)
  - Appropriation Committees
    - Agriculture, 1943-1944 (Box 73)
    - Auburn Beverage Company, 1943-1944 (Box 73)
    - Dairymen's League Association, 1943-1944 (Box 73)
    - Defense, 1943-1944 (Box 73)
    - Fourth Term, 1943-1944 (Box 73)
    - General and Miscellaneous, 1943-1944 (Box 73)
    - Independent Offices, 1943-1944 (Box 73)
    - Legislative, 1943-1944 (Box 73)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1943-1944 (Box 73)
    - TPO, 1943-1944 (Box 73)
    - War, 1943-1944 (Box 73)
    - Ways and Means, 1943-1944 (Box 73)
    - Appropriations, Federal Works Agency, 1947-1949 (Box 113)
    - Appropriations, Federal Works Agency, 1947-1949 (Box 114)
    - Committee Mutual Security, 1954 (Box 86)
    - Bill, making appropriations for the Department of Agriculture and Farm Credit Administrative for fiscal year ending 1956 and with some Taber notations, 1956 (Box 86)
    - Copies of Hearings before Sub-Committee Appropriations Department of Health, Education and Welfare, 1956, 1956 (Box 86)
    - Estimates of Appropriation 1956 National Hediation Board and National Railroad Retirement Board, 1956 (Box 86)
    - Fiscal year 1956 budget estimates, 1956 (Box 86)
    - Hearing Department of Agricultural Appropriations for 1956, part 1, 1956 (Box 86)
    - hose materials on Agriculture, this is printed, and F.C.A. Appropriation Bill,1956, 1956 (Box 86)
    - Salaries and Expenses, National Iabor Relations Board Justification of Appropriation Requests, fiscal year 1956, 1956 (Box 86)
    - U.S. Railroad Retirement Board Justification of Budget Estimates, fiscal year 1956, 1956 (Box 86)
    - Agriculture and Related, 1959 (Box 106)
    - Appropriations: Public Works, 1959 (Box 105)
    - Appropriations: TVA, 1959 (Box 105)
    - Atomic Energy, 1959 (Box 106)
    - Budget, 1959 (Box 106)
    - Byrd Committee, 1959 (Box 106)
    - Commerce and Related, 1959 (Box 106)
    - Committee Membership, 1959 (Box 106)
    - Defense, 1959 (Box 106)
    - Deficiencies and Supps., 1959 (Box 106)
    - District of Columbia, 1959 (Box 106)
    - Foreign Operations, 1959 (Box 106)
    - General Government, 1959 (Box 106)
    - Ind. Offices, 1959 (Box 106)
    - Interior and Related, 1959 (Box 106)
    - Labor, HEW, 1959 (Box 106)
    - Legislative, 1959 (Box 106)
    - Military Construction, 1959 (Box 106)
    - State, Justice, 1959 (Box 106)
    - The Supplement, 1959 (Box 106)
    - Treasury & Post Office, 1959 (Box 106)
    - Appropriations: Public Works, 1960 (Box 105)